megaboutique.com.au 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy

#### INTRODUCTION TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

This web site is subject to the National Privacy Principles under the Australian Privacy Act 1988 (as amended by the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000). This Privacy policy explains in general terms how Mega Boutique protects the privacy of your personal information under the National Privacy Principles. It will apply to any personal information you provide to us when registering with us on our web site www.megaboutique.com.au. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

#### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

The types of personal information that we collect from you will depend on the circumstances of collection and on the type of service you request from us. For example, when you wish to purchase a product from this website we collect details such as your name, address, delivery address, telephone numbers and other information relevant to fulfil your purchase. As we are required by law to obtain your consent to the collection of "sensitive information" (such as address, name and phone number), we will assume that you have given consent to the collection of all information you have provided to us for use in accordance with this Statement, unless you tell us otherwise.

#### HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION

We may collect personal information about you when you visit our website, when you deal with us over the telephone, send us correspondence (whether by letter, fax or email), or when you have contact with us in person. We will not collect any personal information without your consent. We consider that your consent is granted when you complete the forms necessary to facilitate a transaction through this website.

#### HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We generally collect your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To facilitate your access to our website, products and services.
  * To deliver products you have ordered from us.
  * To conduct marketing activities.
  * To provide you with information about our products and services.
  * To seek your opinion on our products, services, marketing and website.
  * To send you a newsletter if you subscribe.

Some of the personal information that we collect is essential for us to be able to accurately identify who is using the service. Other types of personal information we collect help us to develop a profile of who is using our service and what their interests are to assist us in offering products to suit the needs of the users of this website.

#### RESOLVING YOUR CONCERNS

If you wish to gain access to your personal information, have a complaint about a breach of your privacy or you have any query on how your personal information is collected or used please forward your request, complaint or query to the address below. We will respond to your query or complaint as soon as possible. 

Post: The Privacy Officer, 64/170 Forster Road, Mount Waverley 3149 VIC.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may amend this Privacy policy as our business requires or as the law changes. Any changes to this Privacy policy will be updated on www.megaboutique.com.au, so please visit this page periodically to ensure that you have our most current privacy policy.

#### DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

We may disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose for which the information was collected or for related purposes, for example to complete a transaction on your behalf or provide you with a product that you purchased. We engage third party contractors to perform services for us which involves the contractor handling personal information we hold. For example, we currently engage third party contractors to:

  * Deliver products purchased from this website.
  * Provide electronic funds transfer services, credit card account processing and related services.

In these situations, the third party contractor is strictly restricted from using any prohibited personal information about you except for the specific purpose for which we have supplied. We may also disclose your personal information to various law enforcement agencies and governments around the world for security, to comply with a subpoena, customs and immigration purposes. Other than the above, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is either necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, authorised or required by law, reasonably necessary to enforce the law or necessary to investigate a suspected unlawful activity.

#### ACCESS & CORRECTION OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU

We will, on request, provide you with access to the information we hold about you, unless there is an exception which applies under the National Privacy Principles, including for the purpose of correcting or updating that information. We may recover from you our reasonable costs of supplying you with access to this information. Your request to provide access to this information will be dealt with within in a reasonable time. If we refuse to provide you with access to the information, we will provide you with reasons for the refusal and inform you of any exceptions relied upon under the National Privacy Principles.

#### KEEPING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION UP TO DATE

We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete, and up-to-date whenever we collect or use it. If the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date, please contact us and we will take reasonable steps to either correct this information, or if necessary, discuss alternative action with you.

#### COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information. They may further be used by third-party vendors to serve our ads to you across the internet based on your preferences or interests.

#### SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will securely hold your personal information and we will not trade, rent or sell it. 

We will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you. Personal information may be stored both electronically on our computer system, and in hard-copy form. Firewalls, SSL encryption, passwords, anti-virus software and email filters act to protect all our electronic information. We take all necessary measures to ensure the security of hard-copy information. Once your transaction is finalised, both the electronic and hard-copy information are securely archived. After a period of 7 years, both the electronic and hard-copy information will be destroyed.
